University of Connecticut 1998.0153
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IX: Centers and Institutes, 1975-1983
  - Academic Programs, Center for
    - Summer Programs, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 475)
    - Tutoring, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 476)
  - Animal Care Center, 1981-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 477-479)
  - Black Studies, Center For
    - Advisory Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 480-481)
    - General, 1980-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 482-484)
  - Community Education Center, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 485)
  - Computer Applications Center, 1980-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 486-487)
  - Computer Center, 1980-1981 (Box 18:, Folder 488-489)
  - Connecticut Small Business Development Center, 1983 (Box 18:, Folder 490)
  - Education Innovation, Center for, 1980-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 491-492)
  - Energy Center, 1977-1980 (Box 18:, Folder 493)
  - Instructional Media and Technology, Center, 1981-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 494-498)
  - Judaic Studies and Contemporary Jewish Life, Center for, 1981-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 499-500)
  - Labor Education Center, 1981-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 501)
  - Latin American Studies, Center for, 1980-1982 (Box 18:, Folder 502-503)
  - Marine Sciences Institute, 1980-1983 (Box 18:, Folder 504-505)
  - Material Sciences, Institute of, 1980-1983 (Box 19:, Folder 506-509)
  - Middle East Studies, Center for, 1979-1982 (Box 19:, Folder 510-511)
  - Northeast Regional Application Center, 1982 (Box 19:, Folder 512-519)
  - Oral History, Center for, 1981-1982 (Box 19:, Folder 520-521)
  - Policy Science Center, 1981 (Box 19:, Folder 522)
  - Public Service, Institute of, 1982 (Box 19:, Folder 523)
  - Real Estate and Urban Economic Studies Center, 1978-1979 (Box 19:, Folder 524)
  - Slavic and East European Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 19:, Folder 525)
  - Social Inquiry, Institute of, 1977-1983 (Box 19:, Folder 526-529)
  - Technical Services Center, 1979-1983 (Box 19:, Folder 530-533)
  - Transportation Institute, 1975-1980 (Box 19:, Folder 534)
  - Urban Research, Institute of, 1980-1981 (Box 19:, Folder 535)
  - Water Resources, Institute of, 1981-1982 (Box 19:, Folder 536)
  - Wildlife Diseases, Northeastern Research Center for, 1979-1981 (Box 19:, Folder 537)
  - Women's Center, 1981-1982 (Box 19:, Folder 538)
  - World Education Center, 1980-1982 (Box 19:, Folder 539-540)
- Series X: Non-University Organizations, 1978-1983
  - American Association of University Professors, 1980-1983 (Box 20:, Folder 541)
  - American Universities Field Staff, 1978-1981 (Box 20:, Folder 542)
  - Anti-Defamation League, 1979-1980 (Box 20:, Folder 543)
  - Bridgeport, University of, 1979-1981 (Box 20:, Folder 544)
  - Expand Associates Report, 1980 (Box 20:, Folder 545)
  - Klu Klux Klan/INCAR, 1981 (Box 20:, Folder 546)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1981-1982 (Box 20:, Folder 547)
  - Ribicoff Center: Norwich Hospital, 1980 (Box 20:, Folder 548)
  - Tropical Studies, Organization for, 1980-1982 (Box 20:, Folder 549-550)
  - Yale Visiting Faculty Program, 1980-1982 (Box 20:, Folder 551-553)
- Series XI: Outside Agencies, 1978-1982
  - Board of Higher Education, 1980-1981 (Box 21:, Folder 554-561)
  - Board on Higher Education, 1979-1981 (Box 21:, Folder 562-563)
  - Board of State Academic Awards, 1981 (Box 21:, Folder 564)
  - Board of Trustees for State Colleges, 1980 (Box 21:, Folder 565)
  - Board of Trustees: Restructuring of Higher Education, 1979-1980 (Box 21:, Folder 566)
  - Connecticut Conferences of Independent Colleges, 1981 (Box 21:, Folder 567)
  - Connecticut Council on Higher Education, 1981 (Box 21:, Folder 568)
  - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1980-1981 (Box 21:, Folder 569)
  - Connecticut Public Expenditures Council, 1981-1982 (Box 21:, Folder 570)
  - Council of College Presidents/Post Secondary Institutions Consortium, 1978-1980 (Box 21:, Folder 571-572)
  - Coordinating Committee for the North Central Region: Connecticut, 1978-1980 (Box 21:, Folder 573)
  - Coordinating Council for Board of Trustees, 1980 (Box 21:, Folder 574)
  - Governor's Blue Ribbon Council on Higher Education and Economy in Connecticut, 1981 (Box 21:, Folder 575-583)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 584)
  - New England Association for Schools and Colleges, 1980-1981 (Box 22:, Folder 585-586)
  - New England Board of Higher Education, 1980-1981 (Box 22:, Folder 587-588)
  - New England Exchange, 1980-1981 (Box 22:, Folder 589-590)
  - New England Land Grant Universities, 1978-1981 (Box 22:, Folder 591-596)
  - New England State Cooperation, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 597)
  - Office of Policy and Management, 1979-1981 (Box 22:, Folder 598)
- Series XII: Department of Higher Education, 1981-1983
  - Admissions Standards, 1983 (Box 23:, Folder 599)
  - Formula Budgeting, 1982-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 600-604)
  - General, undated (Box 23:, Folder 605)
  - High Technology Project, 1983 (Box 23:, Folder 606)
  - High Technology Continuing Education Task Force, 1981-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 607)
  - Licensure and Accreditation, Special Advisory Committee of, 1983 (Box 23:, Folder 608)
- Series XIII: Faculty Summer Fellowships, 1974-1977
  - 1974-1975 (Box 24:, Folder 609-615)
  - 1975-1977 (Box 24:, Folder 616-622)
    General note
    Return to Provost's Office Records.